Guide to the Yale Objects Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Yale objects collection, 1697-2002; Series I
  - #693 Class of 1881--75th Reunion, blue and white, 1956 (Box 103C, Folder 224)
  - #694 Class of 1881--75th Reunion, blue and white, 1956 (Box 103C, Folder 225)
  - #695 Class of 1881--75th Reunion, blue and white, 1956 (Box 103C, Folder 226)
  - #696 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1864 (Box 103C, Folder 207)
  - #697 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1825 (Box 103C, Folder 228)
  - #698 Senior Mathematical Prize, gold, 1857 (Box 103C, Folder 229)
  - #699 Facsimile of Elihu Yale's seal, undated (Box 103C, Folder 230)
  - #700 Nutmegs--stick pin. Silver nut, 1854 (Box 103C, Folder 231)
  - #701 Nutmeg badge. Wood nut attached to light blue ribbon, 1854 (Box 103C, Folder 232)
  - #702 Die for Phi Beta Kappa key, 1790 (Box 103C, Folder 233)
  - #703 Die for Phi Beta Kappa key, 1797 (Box 103C, Folder 234)
  - #704 Delta Kappa; gold, black, and white crescent, 1882 (Box 103C, Folder 235)
  - #705 Gold watch chain. Phi Beta Kappa key was probably worn on it, 1837 (Box 103C, Folder 236)
  - #706 Tau Epsilon Phi gold key with chain, 1929 (Box 103C, Folder 237)
  - #707 KOW; blue and gold shield, circa 1868 (Box 103D, Folder 238)
  - #708 Gold charm with Hebrew letters, circa 1868 (Box 103D, Folder 239)
  - #709 Delta Kappa Epsilon: gold, black, and white diamond, 1910 (Box 103D, Folder 240)
  - #710 Small gold bracelet: "OCTEPICUREI", 1840 (Box 103D, Folder 241)
  - #711 Phi Beta Psi; gold and black, 1868 (Box 103D, Folder 242)
  - #712 Gold Wolf's Head pin, 1885 (Box 103D, Folder 243)
  - #713 Spoon; gold and silver with engraving of Osborn Hall, undated (Box 103D, Folder 244)
  - #714 Bicentennial pin [copper?] with purple ribbon, 1901 (Box 103D, Folder 245)
  - #715 He Boule; black, white, and gold diamond, 1902 (Box 103D, Folder 246)
  - #716 Bronze charm, "Vicensimus Quintus Yale," with blue cloth and cup, 1892 (Box 103D, Folder 246A)
  - #717 Silver die for a medal, 1787 (Box 103D, Folder 246B)
  - #718 Senior Mathematical Prize, gold, 1877 (Box 103D, Folder 247)
  - #719 81 pin; gold and blue, 1881 (Box 103D, Folder 248)
  - #720 '71 button, white and blue, 1871 (Box 103D, Folder 249)
  - #721 '71 button, blue and gold, 1871 (Box 103D, Folder 250)
  - #722 Theta Xi pin; gold; red and white stones (Box 103D, Folder 251)
  - #723 gold medal, 1830 (Box 103D, Folder 252)
  - #724 Key; Phi Beta Kappa; gold, 1915 (Box 103D, Folder 253)
  - #725 Alpha Delta Phi; black, gold, white, and green, 1915 (Box 103D, Folder 254)
  - #726 Distinguished Service Medal. Gold, red, white, and blue. 4 service ribbons--red, white and blue. 1 lapel button--gold, red, white, and blue, 1918 (Box 103D, Folder 255)
  - #727 [Linonia pin]? gold, 1830 (Box 103D, Folder 256)
  - #728 Saturday Morning Club; gold, white, green, and blue, 1876 (Box 103D, Folder 257)
  - #729 White and gold cloth. Alumni Association of Fairfield County, 1888 (Box 104A, Folder 258)
  - #730 White and gold cloth. Alumni Association of Fairfield County, 1889 (Box 104A, Folder 259)
  - #731 Blue and gold cloth. Alumni Association of Fairfield County, 1889 (Box 104A, Folder 260)
  - #732 Two United Fraternity charms, one diamond shape, one oval shape, both silver, 1786; 1883 (Box 104A, Folder 261)
  - #733 Harvard Badge, 1889. Cloth and metal. Crimson, blue, white, and gold, 1914 (Box 104A, Folder 262)
  - #734 Senior Mathematical Prize, gold. Sample blank, undated (Box 104A, Folder 263)
  - #735 (1) "U.S." (2) "ROTC" (3) blank pins, 1917-1918 (Box 104A, Folder 264)
  - #736 Yale Glee Club, gold, 1884 (Box 104A, Folder 265)
  - #737 '74 class pins. 3 large pins--blue and gold; 2 medium pins--silver and gold; 4 small pins--blue and gold, 1874 (Box 104A, Folder 266)
  - #738 '75 class pins. 1 white and blue; 1 blue and gold, 1875 (Box 104A, Folder 267)
  - #739 '77 class pins. 1 pin with ribbon, 39th reunion, blue, white, and gold; 1 pin, blue and white; 3 lapel buttons, blue and white, 1877 (Box 104A, Folder 268)
  - #740 '81s class buttons (3), blue and silver, 1881 (Box 104A, Folder 269)
  - #741 '83s class pins (2), blue and white, 1883 (Box 104A, Folder 270)
  - #742 '94 class pin, blue and silver, 1894 (Box 104A, Folder 271)
  - #743 Charms, 1906 reunion. In the shape of a "weight." Silver, still in commemorative boxes (Box 104A, Folder 272)
  - #744 1909s reunion pin, blue and white, undated (Box 104A, Folder 273)
  - #745 1911 40th reunion key chain; set with clear plastic, coin on one side, 18780 (Box 104B, Folder 274)
  - #746 1929/1929s reunion pins (2), blue and white, 1949 (Box 104B, Folder 275)
  - #747 Phi Beta Kappa keys--silver; (1) Phi Beta Kappa key--gold, undated (Box 104B, Folder 276)
  - #748 Phi Beta Kappa--Silver Key; Dartmouth, pre 1800 (Box 104B, Folder 277)
  - #749 Die for Phi Beta Kappa key, 1793 (Box 104B, Folder 278)
  - #750 Zeta Phi watch fob; gold with black ribbon, undated (Box 104B, Folder 279)
  - #751 Zeta Theta; gold pin with red and white stones (40, undated (Box 104B, Folder 280)
  - #752 Phi Delta; gold and black (2), undated (Box 104B, Folder 281)
  - #753 2 Kappa Beta Phi gold keys, 1 with chain, 1898 (Box 104B, Folder 282)
  - #754 Fraternity pins: (1) Alpha Sigma Theta; (1) Alpha Delta Chi; (1) Alpha Delta Theta; (1) "Chi", undated (Box 104B, Folder 283)
  - #755 Assorted pins, bicentennial (7), 1901 (Box 104B, Folder 284)
  - #756 Various pins, keys, charms, and buttons (10), undated (Box 104B, Folder 285)
  - #757 Hasty Pudding Club, silver, 1795 (Box 104B, Folder 286)
  - #758 Copper pin with seal; enamel pin--blue, white, and gold, undated (Box 104B, Folder 287)
  - #759 Key to Old Peabody Museum Building (Box 104B, Folder 288)
  - #760 Silver New Haven Tercentennial Spoon, 1938 (Box 104B, Folder 289)
  - #761 Copper medal with cloth, 1908 (Box 104B, Folder 290)
  - #762 Yale-Princeton Football game. Plastic with cloth ribbon, picture of Marshal Foch, 1921 (Box 104B, Folder 291)
  - #763 La Forge L'Union Fait. Gold and blue with blue ribbon in original box, 1882 (Box 104C, Folder 292)
  - #764 Harvard Pin, gold and crimson, undated (Box 104C, Folder 293)
  - #765 Medical Institution of Yale College, Connecticut Medical Society, 1810-1884 Copper medal with blue ribbon, 1913 (Box 104C, Folder 294)
  - #766 Silver and black ribbon with cup, 1894 (Box 104C, Folder 295)
  - #767 Zeta Omicron Alpha; gold with blue stones, 1849 (Box 104C, Folder 296)
  - #768 Gold pin with a globe and the word "Yale" on it. Entwined around the globe is a snake, circa1857 (Box 104C, Folder 297)
  - #769 Souvenir pin from the Yale Bicentennial, 1901 (Box 104C, Folder 298)
  - #770 Visitor's badge or pin from the Yale Bicentennial, 1901 (Box 104C, Folder 299)
  - #771 Watch fob for the Yale Banjo Club, 1896 (Box 104C, Folder 300)
  - #771.1 Two blue and white reunion buttons, Yale 1912, 1896 (Box 104C, Folder 301)
  - #772 Reunion button, '09s. Name [Joe Knapp]? inscribed, undated (Box 104C, Folder 302)
  - #773 Taft Presidential Campaign Buttons (9), 1909 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - #774 Souvenir pin from the inauguration of William H. Taft as President, 1909 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - #775 Souvenir pin from the inauguration of William H. Taft as President. A photograph of Taft is attached by a red, white, and blue ribbon to the pin, 1909 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - #776 Heart-shaped souvenir pin from Taft's inauguration, 1909 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - #777 Souvenir pin in the shape of a key which reads "Inauguration of President William H. Taft. Key of the White House.", 1909 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - #778 Inaugural Chorus pin from Taft and Sherman's Inauguration, 1909 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - #779 Ribbon which reads: "Historic Sites--Inauguration of William H. Taft, 1909." (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - #780 Ribbon which reads: "Floor Aide--Missouri--Inauguration of William H. Taft, 1909" (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - #781 Ribbon showing a likeness of Wm. H. Taft with the words: "For President, Wm. H. Taft", 1909 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - #782 Piece from the rafter of Block House at San Juan Hill, 1898 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - #783 Oval-shaped piece of metal which shows either the U.S.S. Squalus of the U.S.S. Thornback, circa 1940s (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - #784 Chain with a golf-tee like object on one end and a charm on the other, undated (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - #785 Relief portrait of A. Brizeux; plaster, undated (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - #786 Wooden plaque with the coat of arms of [?], undated (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - #787 Various sizes of copper engraving plates from the estate of Lucius Fitch--uses were unknown, undated (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - #788 Set of six Wedgwood plates; green and white, in relief floral border. Views of New Haven: Hillhouse Avenue, East Rock, Harbor, Judges' Cave, the Green, circa 1931 (Box 106, Folder 1-6)
  - #789 Engraving plate of New Haven Green, undated (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - #790 Linen apron, dance souvenir, dance program, 10th annual Calico Hall Ball, New Haven. At the Music Hall, 1870 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - #791 Wooden fraternity handle which reads: Laurence H. Norton 1910 from... ", 1908 (Box 106)
  - #792 Embroidered flour bag which was packed with flour as a war relief donation, circa 1915 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - #793 Blue megaphone with the decal of Eddie Wittstein's Orchestra on the front, undated (Box 106)
  - #794 Lenox china bulldog, Yale blue, created especially for Benjamin C. Grieb (Y. 1921) as a gift from John M. Tossie of Lenox, [1943-1945]? (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - #795 Yale blue silk handkerchief with light blue Y in center and in corner, undated (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - #796 Yale blue cotton. Printed on edges. "PROTECTION-TRUE BLUE-HOME INDUSTRIES REPUBLICAN", undated (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - #797 Yale blue tie with AYA pattern. Necktie given by the AYA to all male Assembly Representatives (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - #798 Metal die of the Class seal for 1863 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - #799 Wooden plaque "SIGILL: COLL: YALEN: NOV: PORT: NOV: ANGL", undated (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - #800 Yale 1901 Banner (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - #801 2 white. In blue and red, "YH the 100th GAME" Yale-Harvard, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - #802 Red, white and blue bag with insignia of the 100th football game of Yale-Harvard, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - #803 Light blue sweater with insignia of the 100th football game of Yale-Harvard, 1983 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - #804 Glasses with the insignia of 100th football game, Yale vs. Harvard, 1983 (Box 110)
  - #805 Plaster of Paris head of John Spangler Nicholas, Professor of Anatomy, undated (Box 111)
  - #806 Brocade table runner, labeled "Kawashima Kyoto, Japan." (Box 84)
  - #807 Silver cigarette box with Karl Carstens autograph engraved on it, 1983 October 14 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - #808 Framed Photograph with autograph of Karl Carstens, 1983 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - #809 Water color painting. Blue flowers with butterfly. 1 pamphlet: "Southwest Teachers College--A Brief Introduction." 18 postcards of the college, 1983 (Box 114)
  - #810 Plaque in honor of "Edward Stephen Harkness, Beta Chapter of Psi Upsilon 1897... ", 1952 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - #811 Plaque in honor of "Amos Edward Lawrence... ", 1952 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - #812 2 1/4" Achromatic Refractor by Banks of London Brass Telescope. Possibly the "glass" used by Ezra Stiles to observe British landing at Savin Rock in 1779, circa 1780
    Transferred to Peabody Museum; part of Yale Collection of Historical Scientific Instruments; YPM 10441
  - #813 Walking sticks belonging to Mary Alden Loomis and E.F. Loomis. Various Maine resort area names carved in them, 1902, 1905, undated (Box 394)
  - #814 Metal kneeling hunter whose gun expels pith balls, giving the effect of shooting. Electrostatic toy, circa 1800s
  - #815 Electrostatic Treadmill, circa 1800s
    Transferred to Peabody Museum; part of Yale Collection of Historical Scientific Instruments; YPM 10443
  - #816 Exploding house, "thunder house"; was used to show the importance of equipping buildings with lightning rods, circa 1800s
    Transferred to Peabody Museum; part of Yale Collection of Historical Scientific Instruments; YPM 10387
  - #817 Asymmetrical top. Made by Newton & Co. (3 pieces), circa 1800s
    Transferred to Peabody Museum; part of Yale Collection of Historical Scientific Instruments;YPM 10444A, YPM 10444B
  - #818 Sextant made by Banks of London. In wooden box. Owned by Elias Loomis, circa 1835
    Transferred to Peabody Museum; part of Yale Collection of Historical Scientific Instruments; YPM 10409
  - #819 Edward Hooker's lap desk. Made in New Haven, 1818. Contains 1 inkbottle, 1 ink drying shaker bottle, 1 seal, 2 buton hole buttons. Made of bird's eye maple (Box 118A)
  - #820 Clockwork Heliostat. Engraved "Presented to Yale College by Edward S. Fellow." The mirror, moved by clockwork, was designed to reflect the sun's rays in a fixed direction, circa 1850 (Box 119)
  - #821 Burned-down blue candle from 25th reunion dinner of the Class of 1936. Sits on a piece of wood, 1961 (Box 120)
  - #822 Connecticut Hall (South Middle) key mounted on wood. Returned to University by Carrington A Phelps, undated (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - #823 Key to Old Chapel porch with its original tag on vellum. Old Chapel stood on the Old Campus between North Middle and North Colleges 1824-1896, circa 1824 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - #824 Noah Porter key, undated (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - #825 Large unidentified key, undated (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - #826 Metal Key, Yale seal on top--"NP" cut through key part. Engraved "Key to the Porter Gateway, Original Presented to Miss Jenning. By the Yale Corp.... ", 1913 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - #827 Plaque of a wooden scroll and wooden key (Scroll and Key secret society), 1859 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - #828 Tobacco pouches, 1924, 1937 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - #829 Red ribbon with gold "The Century 1847-1897" (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - #830 Reunion pin 1919s (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - #831 Yale Bicentennial ribbons with pins 1701-1901 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - #832 Class of 1882, 1917 reunion pin with American flag ribbon with 13 stars (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - #833 Medal. Bank of Pittsburgh 100th Anniversary, 1910 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - #834 Medal. Relief of Dollie Bell Whiley, 1911 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - #835 Door from Connecticut Hall. Many names and dates written and carved in it, circa 1800s
  - #836 Unidentified plaque with fish with ring, tree, bird, book, bell and candle holder, undated (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - #837 Metal round box with head of Christopher Columbus. 1492 Chicago USA, 1892 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - #838 Metal cup with chain attached at the bottom. [Communal cup for a pump], good (Box 123)
  - #839 Glass with yellow and black decal of a Viking-type boat (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - #840 Streamers, pink and gold, red, blue. [flag pole knob]?, undated (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - #841 Press, Department of Military Science, undated (Box 124)
  - #842 Y '92 medal attached to blue and white ribbon with clip, 1892 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - #843 Unidentified tea spoon, undated (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - #844 Clear glass jar with top. Small container inside; contents of both unknown, undated (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - #845 Letter opener made from "Yale Oak 1752 from Connecticut Hall." Taken into space by Joseph P. Allen aboard the Space Shuttle "Columbia" 11/11-16/1982 (Box 327)
  - #846 Wooden walking stick. Carved handle. Chinese male figure with a large bird. Inscription in family name Chiang, undated (Box 308)
  - #847 Framed black and gold sign: "YALE UNIVERSITY--NEW HAVEN", undated
  - #848 Bust of Joel Barlow, (Y. 1778), cast from original by Jean Antoine Houdon, undated
  - #849 Wooden table with octagonal top, center post with three legs, undated
  - #850 Bust of Roger Sherman, Honorary M.A, 1768. By Willard Paddock, 1937
  - #851 Bust of William Howard Taft, (Y. 1878), cast from original by Bryant Baker, 1922
  - #852 Bust of Noah Webster, (Y. 1778) by Chauncey Bradley Ives, undated
  - #853 Bust of Henry Farnam by Margaret E. Foley, 1868
  - #854 Bust of Jermiah Day (Y. 1795), by Chauncey Bradley Ives, 1842
  - #855 Ezra Stiles' grandfather clock of English oak. Glass-enclosed metal face, marked "John Garland, London." Door on front--inside, pendulum and weights, circa 1766
    Transferred to the Yale Art Gallery.
  - #856 Wooden table with octagonal top, center post with three legs, undated
  - #857 Wooden table with octagonal top, center post with three legs, undated
  - #858 Desk belonging to Colonel Edward House, drop-front with four drawers below. Inside, seven small drawers, four pigeon-holes, undated
  - #859 Desk belonging to James Rowland Angell. Center drawer, four drawers on either side, undated
  - #860 Blue cloth banner with "Yale" printed in white, undated (Box 196)
  - #861 Metal bust of Frank Polk mounted on marble block
  - #862 Plaster cast, possibly death mask of Napoleon, undated (Box 229)
  - #863 John Rogers' group of Yale Football--statue of 4 men playing football, undated (Box 193)
  - #864 Wooden sign in frame: "Luzon B. Morris Attorney at Law.", undated
  - #865 Wooden plaque with raised letter CSP on top, CCJ on bottom, and raised scroll and key. Probably from Scroll and Key, undated (Box 172)
  - #866 Glass inkwell with black plastic cover, undated (Box 234)
  - #867 Glass dome-shaped jar with small opening at top, undated
  - #868 2 pieces: small glass dish; glass lid flattened globe-shaped, knob on top, small opening in bottom, undated
  - #869 Wooden table with octagonal top, center post with three legs, undated
  - #870 Wooden table with octagonal top, center post with three legs, inkwell hole in top, undated
  - #871 Wooden table with octagonal top, center post with three legs, undated
  - #872 White china with blue design. Yale scene with trees, people, New Haven Green and State House. Floral border, undated (Box 328)
  - #873 White china with blue design. Yale scene with trees, people, New Haven Green and State House. Floral border, undated
  - #874 Jackson Ware bowl depicting Yale and the State House, floral pattern, rose on white. "Jackson's Warranted" mark (Box 329)
  - #875 Blue pattern on white, depicting Yale and the State House, floral borders. Two handles. Four legs. Oval shape, undated (Box 330)
  - #876 Metal cup with handle, made from beer can. Paper label with design of bulldog by Richard C. Yorkey, (Y. 1949) Caption: "Derby Day." Sold for Derby Day 1949 (Box 331)
  - #877 Ceramic mug with picture of football player and insignia. Brown glaze. Handle. Signed "F. Earl Christy", undated (Box 332)
  - #878 Blue ribbon with silver printing. Picture of football player with "YALE" written at top, undated
  - #879 Blue mug, gold borders on rim, base, and handle. Gold Yale seal. On bottom, mark: "Lenox, Glouskin and Fox, New Haven", undated (Box 333)
  - #880 Marble bust of Dickens, undated (Box 334)
  - #881 Brass figurine of Nathan Hale. On base: "Nathan Hale," "Sons of the Revolution," "November 25-1893," and "New York." (Box 335)
  - #882 Ticket to first Yale-Harvard football game, in frame, 1875
  - #883 Brass bust of Paul M. Warburg by Malvina Hoffmann on a black wooden cube pedestal, 1933 (Box 336)
  - #884 Diploma case: Black metal tube with top, silver printing: "YALE" with border, undated (Box 337)
  - #885 Brass letter-opener with owl at top of handle. Inscription on blade: "YALE Bicentennial, 1701-1901, New Haven." Yale insignia, circa 1901 (Box 338)
  - #886 White clay pipe with long, curved stem. Pipe bowl has knob on bottom. Stem broken in half. End of stem painted brown, undated (Box 339)
  - #887 White clay pipe with bumpy design on bowl, end of stem painted red. Straight stem, undated (Box 340)
  - #888 White clay pipe with long curved stem. Bowl has knob on bottom, undated (Box 341)
  - #889 White clay pipe with long curved stem. Bowl has knob on bottom. End of stem painted brown. Blue label on stem: "Gouda-Holland-Goedewaagen's PIJP", undated (Box 342)
  - #890 White clay pipe. Blue label on stem: "Gouda-Holland-Goedewaagen's PIJP." Straight stem, undated (Box 343)
  - #891 Small rectangular paper package, "Falk's Serene Mixture." Green/white/gold, 1910 (Box 344)
  - #892 Tan leather with blue strings, blue design on front: flag with Y, undated (Box 344)
  - #893 Matchbook with blue and red printing. Front "University Smoke Shop, Everything for the Smoker.. .", undated
  - #894 Ashtray shaped like a shell with picture of Osborn Hall in color. Dark blue and gold border on sides. On bottom: "Made in Germany... ", undated (Box 345)
  - #895 (Empty) album with black wooden back. Front painted with picture of Brick Row and State House (Box 346)
  - #896 Wooden table with octagonal top, center post with three legs, undated
  - #897 Metal statue of Col. House, sitting. By Cathleen Scoott, undated (Box 347)
  - #898 Metal bust of Sir Walter Scott. On back: "Studied from the Chantry Bust, Thomas Lawrance's picture, and the Death Mask. C. Colnerly, SC 1896." (Box 348)
  - #899 Marble statue of [Aristides]?, 1861 (Box 349)
  - #900 Pottery pitcher, tan with blue flower design (one flower) on front; handle; glazed brown inside, undated (Box 366)
  - #901 Wooden table with octagonal top, center post with three legs, undated
  - #902 Carved ivory box, lined with red velvet. Keyhole in front; 4 small legs carved into faces; On bottom: "Edward & Esther, to be.. ." Inside, white handkerchief, undated (Box 350)
  - #903 View of Old Campus from Chapel St. looking North, undated
  - #904 View of Old Brick Row from New Haven Green. By L.M. Wool, undated
    Item transferred to the Yale University Art Gallery
  - #905 Portrait of William Boardman, Yale Alumnus, in gold wood frame, undated
  - #906 Flat black case with wooden front, back. Yale College scene on cones, undated (Box 351)
  - #907 Blue "Yale" button with white letters, white ribbon and red ribbon attached, undated (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - #908 Yale reunion ID button, white with blue border, "YALE" at top. Written in: "H.H. Myers, '20.", undated (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - #909 Blue and white bulldog patch, undated (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - #910 Blue baseball cap with white patch on front: "Yale 1920's", undated (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - #911 Bottle cork with carved wooden Yale bulldog on top, wearing blue and white Yale shirt and hat, undated (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - #912 Brass door knocker: Top has Yale seal and "Lux et Veritas," bottom has bulldog head and "YALE". Also, 2 screws, undated (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - #913 Class Day 1916 tobacco pouch. Blue printing "Class Day--Yale--1916" (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - #914 Cut of Dunham Lab, undated (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - #915 Small red/white/blue button, "Democrat for Wilkie.", undated (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - #916 Small red/white/blue button, "Democrat for Wilkie.", undated (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - #917 Patch commemorating space shuttle Columbia flight--picture of shuttle orbiting globe, another shuttle flying upwards, words "Columbia" and "Young-Crippen.", 1981 (Box 173)
  - #918 Cloth American flag (mounted with a patch, object #917, on blue board), 1981 (Box 173)
  - #919 Blue cloth ribbon with "12-6" (score of Yale/Harvard game) accompanied by printed note, 1890 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - #920 Silver pitcher with round, flat base, handle. Engraved: "Presented to Henry Barnard... ", circa 1849 (Box 127)
  - #921 3-handled loving cup, engraved "Charles G. Rockwood--Presented by his classmates as a testamonial... " Blue and white Yale seal, Yale '64 crest, circa 1899 (Box 127)
  - #922 Silver bowl. On bottom, marked "Tiffany & Co." and engraved "Hollon A. Fan, with the affection of the Class of 1938", circa 1938 (Box 127)
  - #923 Silver loving cup with 2 handles. "Class of 1873 Yale" engraved on base, names of class members engraved on cup, circa 1873 (Box 128)